WORLDLY DESIRES
(世俗雜念)
TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-
《妙廟美少女》
(Extra 1: How Can It Be So Big?)
(番外一 不是吧 怎麼會這麼大…)
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE
(三日月寺)
Th-Th-This…
這…
What the hell is going on?
這是怎麼回事啊
Why is this Akagami's body?
這是什麼鬼 是赤神的身體嗎
What's happening?
怎麼回事
Once I opened my eyes, I was already Akagami.
一覺醒來我就變成赤神了
It's not a dream…
這不是夢…
How can it be so big?
不是吧 怎麼會這麼大
I swear I did not entertain any sexist thoughts…
我明明完全沒在想色色的事情…
I-I've turned into Miss Yuzuki.
我 我變成結月小姐了
Breasts…
奶子…
Worldly desires, begone!
雜念退散
No, no.
不行不行
How could I possibly hurt Miss Yuzuki's sweet face?
我怎麼能讓結月小姐 最寶貴的臉蛋受傷呢
But then again,
話說回來
she is stunning.
她還真是美麗啊
But what should I do?
但我究竟該怎麼辦…
Kurage?
海月…
Akagami.
赤神哥哥
Shall we get married?
我們結婚吧
I want to make this a reality.
我想和你把生米煮成熟飯
H-Hold on.
等…等等
Akagami, you have been checked.
這樣我就將軍了呢 赤神
Wait, wait.
等等…
I am still a child.
海月還是個小孩子
Getting caught for what you did to me
如果被人發現你對她做出這種事
would be the end of your life.
那你的人生也要告一段落了
I said hold on!
我都叫妳等一下了
Oh dear.
哎呀哎呀
You want to do this to me?
竟然對海月起反應
You're really a lolicon.
你還真是蘿莉控啊
No way.
討厭
What is up? You are acting kind of weird.
你怎麼了 反應有夠奇怪
By any chance, are you Kagura?
妳難道是…神樂嗎
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE
(三日月寺)
It seems
看來
everyone's been swapped.
大家的人格都交換了呢
Is it possible that this thing could happen?
這世上真的有這種事嗎
This is, after all, an established reality.
畢竟這已經是事實了
Why would this happen?
到底是為什麼呢
Why?
為什麼…
Incense?
薰香嗎
This is from Baldwin.
這是我家裡寄來的東西
It seems very suspicious.
總覺得很可疑…
Should we burn the incense right away?
事不宜遲 我們就來焚香吧
I originally intended
我本來是想
to make Mia a more lewd character.
讓米亞變成色色的性格的
Is it all because of you?
這都是神樂妳害的嗎
You caught me.
欸嘿嘿
Anyway, we have to find everyone.
總之 我們必須找到大家才行
Surely now everyone is in distress.
大家現在一定很困擾
We can't let this go on.
不能繼續這樣下去了
Anyway, I have to get dressed first.
總之我要先換衣服
Dress appropriately for Miss Yuzuki.
換上適合結月小姐儀容的衣服…
No bra…
沒穿胸罩…
Adult…
大人…
THE LAW OF THE JUNGLE
(弱肉強食)
Mature…
成熟…
Akagami, look.
(錄影) 赤神哥哥…你看…
Kurage?
海月
You are Kurage, aren't you?
妳果然是海月吧
Could you please save this video?
麻煩妳把剛剛的錄影存下來哦
Me… in front of myself…
我看到了自己
It is incredible.
真是不可思議
This Mia has a new vibe.
這樣的米亞還挺新鮮的呢
Kurage, please attend the family meeting later.
海月 妳等下過來開個家庭會議
Sis Yuzuki?
妳是結月姐姐嗎
Don't you think you should give some thought to the thing you filmed?
妳拍的這個 是不是需要稍微反省一下呢
I'm Mia now.
我現在是米亞…的說
Oh well, if it's Mia, we can't help it.
是嗎 既然妳是米亞 那就沒辦法了
Mia claims she is on a diet.
米亞說她正在減肥呢
The parishioner has sent
難得有施主
a delicious Yokan.
送來了很好吃的羊羹呢
Yokan!
羊羹
No sexy selfies, okay?
妳不可以拍色色的自拍照哦
I'm sorry.
對不起
It is admirable that you can admit wrongdoing.
還好妳誠實認錯了
So I will delete the video.
那我就把錄影刪掉…
Yaaa!
啊…
It's my scream.
是我的慘叫聲
THE LAW OF THE JUNGLE
(弱肉強食)
Find a way out of an impasse.
置之死地而後生
This way, I will not have to witness the stripping.
這樣就算我不看 我也能脫衣服了
Oh dear.
討厭
My, my.
哎呀哎呀
Wait, Kiki, stop it!
等等 嬉嬉姐 住手啊
Nyagosuke?
是喵…仔嗎
I see.
原來如此
Kiki and Nyagosuke have switched.
嬉嬉姐和喵仔的人格互換了
Could you be
莫非妳是…
Tsukuyo?
月夜嗎
Are you Tsukuyo?
妳是月夜嗎
Don't look at me.
不要看我
I will never forgive you.
我絕對不會原諒妳…
Why are you mad?
妳生什麼氣嘛
Oh dear. What a racket.
哎呀哎呀 真是吵鬧啊
It's talking!
牠說話了
What's wrong with the cat talking?
貓貓說話有什麼不好
There's nothing wrong, Nyagosuke is the cutest.
沒什麼不好 喵仔最可愛了
I am Kiki.
我是嬉嬉
Scratch, scratch.
抓抓
I am Kiki!
我是嬉嬉呀
Let's give you some milk.
給妳喝點牛奶吧
Could you please change it to wine?
拜託給我換成酒
I'm talking to her.
我是在對牠說啦
As expected of me, that's kind of erotic.
不愧是我 真是色情啊
Nyagosuke.
喵仔
You always go to sleep after you finish your milk.
總是喝完牛奶後就會去睡覺
Ignore her for the time being.
暫時先不用管她了
Let us go find
趁現在
everyone now.
我們去找其他人吧
Wait.
等等
What's wrong?
妳怎麼了
Um… Well…
嗯…那個…
Even though I ran away directly just now,
雖然我剛剛直接跑了
but Akagami may also
但是赤神
have exchanged with someone.
他也有可能跟誰交換人格了
WC
(廁所)
What are you guys doing?
你們在幹嘛啊
What should I do?
廁所到底要怎麼上啊
I cannot keep going like this.
一直這樣下去也不是辦法
I need to get dressed quickly.
我必須要快點換衣服了
Miss Yuzuki
結月小姐穿起來
looks best in…
最漂亮的衣服
Kimono?
是和服嗎
But if I wear a kimono…
但是穿和服的話
Down there…
下面也要…
So shy.
討厭
Temporary illusion, just temporary illusion.
一時的錯覺一時的錯覺
This must be my temporary illusion…
這絕對是我一時的錯覺…
It's reality.
這是現實啊
Mia?
米亞
Surely you must be Mia.
妳是米亞吧
Are you Miss Yuzuki?
妳是…結月小姐嗎
Thank God, you're okay.
還好妳沒事
Everyone else appears to have swapped as well.
這就表示大家也都交換人格了…
I myself am here too.
我看到我自己了
I'm Kurage.
我是海月哦
I'm Kagura.
我是神樂
What's that for?
那是什麼
We had a dangerous situation to handle.
我們剛才處理了有點危險的東西
That is quite impressive!
你這雄壯的傢伙
Kiki.
嬉嬉姐
Master?
師父
I would like to be hit by a meow punch as well!
我也想挨一記喵喵拳
Stop! That's my body!
住手呀 那是我的身體
What exactly does "impressive" mean?
雄壯是什麼
Kurage, stop asking.
海月妳別問了
Rather,
比起這個
we need to gather everyone.
我們必須得找到大家才行
Miss Yuzuki,
還沒找到的就只有…
you are the only one who has not been found.
結月小姐妳自己了
Crap! You've swapped with Akagami!
糟了 妳和赤神交換了
It is likely that Akagami went someplace
現在赤神肯定
like a bathroom.
去了廁所之類的地方
Your worries will naturally vanish
只要心中毫無雜念
if you clear your mind of all distractions!
煩惱自然會消失
I am not
現在的我
Akagami Akemitsu right now,
並不是赤神明光
I am Miss Yuzuki.
而是結月小姐
I am Miss Yuzuki, the most wonderful woman on the planet.
我是這個世界上最出色的女性 結月小姐啊
So there are no distractions for me!
所以我根本不會感覺到任何雜念
Sis Yuzuki is also quite lustful.
結月姐姐也很色色哦
Please do not show up at this time, Miss Kurage.
妳不要在這時候出現啊 海月小姐
Introverted Sis Yuzuki, huh.
結月姐姐很悶騷哦
I am not going to let you do whatever you want, distractions.
雜念啊 我不會放任你胡來的
I'm not mature anymore.
我不再成熟了
That is to say…
這麼說
We have changed back.
我們變回來了
You guys.
你們幾個
Master?
師父
How is it? Have you all changed back?
怎麼樣 你們都變回去了嗎
How about you?
嬉嬉姐呢
You are still a little like a cat.
妳還是有點像貓呢
Meow meow.
喵喵
Stop making fun of me.
妳別鬧了
It appears that the effect fades with time.
看來隨著時間流逝 效果就會消失呢
So I will have to think carefully about how to use it.
那麼我就需要 再仔細考慮一下使用方法了
Akagami, where's Sis Yuzuki?
對了 赤神 結月姐呢
Just now you exchanged with Sis Yuzuki, right?
你剛才和結月姐交換人格了 對吧
Then you should know where she is.
那你應該最清楚她在哪了
Um… Hmm…
呃…那個嘛…
Well.
那個
I have been in her room the whole time…
我一直都在結月小姐的房間裡…
Let's go, everyone.
各位 我們走吧
W-Wait!
等等 等一下
I gave up changing clothes.
我放棄了換衣服
In order to suppress my own distractions, I…
為了抑制自己的雜念 我就把自己…
Is everyone there?
大家都在那裡嗎
Have you all changed back?
你們都變回來了嗎
What I see is completely dark.
我眼前一片漆黑
And why am I immobilized?
而且為什麼我動不了啊
I'm very sorry, Miss Yuzuki.
結月小姐 非常抱歉
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE Ah!
(三日月寺) 啊…